[Music]
[音乐]
so good evening everyone see some people
晚上好，大家见到一些人
still taking some seats so take your
还在坐着，所以请坐
time
时间
good evening so last session of today I
晚上好，今天最后一堂
hope you all had a great day today and
希望大家今天过得愉快
you learned a lot of great stuff so what
你学到了很多很棒的东西
I want to talk to you about together
我想和你谈谈
with my colleague here it's about
和我的同事在这里
service as so it was now about two years
服务，所以现在大约两年了
ago I think that I first got introduced
以前我认为我是第一次被介绍的
to the term invisible infrastructure it
隐性基础设施一词
was at a conference where we were
在我们参加的会议上
talking about what the new things were
谈论什么是新事物
about the new hot topics were about for
关于新的热门话题是关于
the coming year and I was really curious
来年，我真的很好奇
about the term at that time I already
关于当时的学期
knew some stuff about function as a
知道一些有关功能的知识
service I tried some hello world
服务我尝试了一些世界
experience with that but this idea of
经验，但是这个想法
helping of or getting some help in
帮助或得到一些帮助
creating our applications where we can
在我们可以的地方创建我们的应用程序
really focus on the business logic and
真正专注于业务逻辑和
and we need the added value that's lies
我们需要的是附加值
for our company really intrigued me and
因为我们公司真的吸引了我，
so it is in that case that we as a
所以在这种情况下，我们作为一个
company also did some more investigating
公司还做了更多调查
in this topic in our Belgian company we
在我们比利时公司的这个主题中，我们
were mainly focused on spring technology
主要集中在Spring 技术上
we have a lot of people really experts
我们真的有很多人是专家
in this domain and so it was really nice
在这个领域，所以真的很好
to take a look at what can spring do
看看 Spring 能做什么
also in this topic about serverless as
同样在本主题中，关于无服务器
well and so this is also something that
好，所以这也是
we try to figure out in this
我们试图找出这一点
presentation now as I said before it's
现在就像我之前所说的那样
an interesting topic because it helps us
一个有趣的话题，因为它可以帮助我们
it can help us as a developer to create
它可以帮助我们作为开发人员来创建
new applications also a lot of companies
新应用也很多公司
are already more or less interested in
已经或多或少对
this and at this time about 10% of the
这个，目前大约是10％
companies already have something to do
公司已经有事要做
with function or service architecture
具有功能或服务架构
and regarding to some numbers from
关于一些数字
Gartner next year in the coming years we
Gartner明年在未来的几年中，我们
will only see more and more companies
只会看到越来越多的公司
interested in this topic
对这个话题感兴趣
so there must be something going on here
所以这里一定有事
and now the thing is we don't think that
现在的事情是我们不认为
service will be something that you will
服务将是您所需要的
use for every application but it will be
用于每个应用程序，但它将
something like in a tool on your tool
就像工具上的工具一样
belt that you can use in certain cases
在某些情况下可以使用的皮带
and so in fact that's what this talk is
所以实际上这就是这个话题
all about we wanted to investigate a
关于我们的全部要调查
little bit what what is a proper place
一点什么是合适的地方
for using this kind of tools and so we
使用这种工具，所以我们
really wanted to get our hands dirty now
真的很想现在弄脏我们的手
it doesn't need really mean that you
并不需要真的意味着你
should now go home and immediately start
现在应该回家并立即开始
migrating your application to a service
将您的应用程序迁移到服务
environment because that's probably not
环境，因为那可能不是
the best for every case here and so
最适合这里的每种情况
don't try this at home if you haven't
如果没有，不要在家尝试
really thought about this and experience
真的考虑过这个和经验
sharing is of course something that can
分享当然可以
help you make a decision this way so I
这样可以帮助您做出决定，所以我
hope you all get something out of this
希望大家从中得到一些东西
talk after today and maybe already
今天以后再说，也许已经
introduced it maybe in some specific
介绍了它也许在某些特定的
projects or maybe you're already doing
项目或也许您已经在做
surveillance at the moment so just out
目前正在监视，所以刚出来
of curiosity who is already doing a
好奇心的人已经在做
service application in production at
生产中的服务应用程序
this moment okay some people yeah
这一刻好吧，有人
right now before we get on it's maybe
现在我们开始之前
good to have a good baseline to start
有一个良好的基准开始很好
from what is service architecture
从什么是服务架构
because there are a lot of terms
因为有很多条款
terminologies and and different
术语和和不同
definitions out there well in our
我们的定义很好
opinion service architecture is really
意见服务架构真的
all about two things namely the first
关于两件事，即第一件事
one is function as a service where you
一种是作为服务的功能
are going to just create some code and
将只创建一些代码，
just have it run on a platform without
只是让它在没有
having to worry really about the
不必担心
underlying infrastructure regarding
有关的基础架构
servers and things that have to be set
服务器和必须设置的东西
up to make your code run the second
使您的代码第二次运行
thing and that is something that is not
东西，那不是
always that clear in my opinion is that
我认为总是很清楚的是
it also means that you're going to try
这也意味着您要尝试
to leverage the platform as much as
充分利用平台
possible but because of course if you
可能，但是因为如果你
still have to maybe set up a lot of
仍然必须建立很多
extra stuff doing security and other
额外的东西做安全和其他
services that you might need for support
您可能需要的支持服务
in your application then again you're
在您的应用程序中，然后您再次
really getting away from the focus which
真正摆脱焦点
is again the business logic of your
再次是您的业务逻辑
application and so beckoned as a service
应用程序，因此被视为服务
is really a very important part in my
是我中非常重要的一部分
opinion as well towards having a full
意见也要充分
service architecture now that of course
现在的服务架构
comes with a lot of costs because it
伴随着很多成本，因为它
means so it might mean that you will tie
意味着，这可能意味着你会打成平手
your application a little bit more
您的应用程序多一点
towards a certain platform so you have
对某个平台，所以你有
to make of course a decision if that's
当然可以决定是否
something what you want and if that can
你想要的东西，如果可以的话
maybe have some impact on your decision
可能对您的决定有影响
or your business now we said we can just
或您现在的业务，我们说我们可以
go on and keep implementing these
继续并继续执行这些
HelloWorld examples but really that
HelloWorld示例，但确实如此
doesn't give you the real value of
并没有给您真正的价值
course creating an application that can
当然创建一个可以
be run that is based on maybe an
运行可能基于
existing application where we want to
我们想要的现有应用程序
have all the functionality being
具有所有功能
translated towards service and so really
转化为服务，所以真的
got our hands dirty and we said why not
弄脏了我们的手，我们说为什么不
try to migrate an existing application
尝试迁移现有的应用程序
that we have and see what kind of
我们有，看看什么样的
problems we run into how we can overcome
我们遇到的问题如何克服
them and maybe some of them are just not
他们，也许其中一些不是
a good fit and so that was really all
非常合适，这就是全部
about this ID that we had as we had a
关于我们拥有的这个ID
typical web application with some web
具有某些Web的典型Web应用程序
sockets in there
那里的插座
a database some security setup and so on
数据库一些安全设置等等
and so we'll discuss in a minute a
所以我们待会儿讨论
little bit more about the architecture
有关体系结构的更多信息
and of course also we wanted to look out
当然我们也要注意
what what is out there so what kind of
那里是什么，那是什么样的
platforms do we have what kind of
我们有什么样的平台
tooling what kind of frameworks are out
工具出什么样的框架
there and so we hope you can also
在那里，所以我们希望您也可以
leverage a little bit from that
从中利用一点点
experience today and so we're going to
今天的经验，所以我们要
talk about some of them of course also
说说其中的一些当然
scalability is one of the ideas we will
可扩展性是我们将要提出的想法之一
talk about the application in the
在
minutes where we can briefly discuss on
分钟，我们可以简要讨论
that and also of course again because
那当然也是因为
we're a company that specialized in
我们是一家专门从事
spring technology we wanted to look out
我们要关注的Spring 技术
what is the support and spring can help
有什么支持， Spring 可以帮助您
us with for creating such applications
我们一起创建这样的应用程序
well there is of course a risk we are
好吧，我们当然有风险
going to do a migration so you could
要进行迁移，这样您就可以
maybe think I'm going to do a one-on-one
也许以为我要一对一地做
migration and just take everything that
迁移并承担一切
I have and just make sure that it runs
我有并确保它运行
somewhere as a function maybe just have
某个功能可能只是
one function and I just put everything
一个功能，我就把所有东西
in there that's of course not a good
在那当然不是很好
idea and so we really wanted to make
这个想法，所以我们真的很想
sure that we leverage everything that is
确保我们充分利用一切
out there and so we try to free our
在那里，所以我们尝试释放我们的
minds a little bit and see that we can
稍微思考一下，看看我们可以
do some investigation what is out there
做一些调查那里有什么
what can help us how do we translate one
什么可以帮助我们如何翻译一个
thing from another and so on so please
从另一个东西等等，所以请
bear with us if we go on with this maybe
如果我们继续下去，请和我们一起忍受
some experimental topics might come into
一些实验性的话题可能会出现
play here and yeah well you have to be
在这里玩，好吧，你必须
open for it and of course make sure to
打开它，当然要确保
see how you are going to implement it at
看看您将如何实现它
your company now what we want to talk
您的公司现在我们要谈什么
about today is an application which was
今天大约是一个应用程序
a slot reservation system and it's all
插槽预订系统
about pigs which you might have read
关于你可能已经读过的猪
also in the description of this talk the
同样在这个谈话的描述中
idea is in fact that we have some kind
实际上，我们有某种想法
of reservation websites which you can
可以预订的网站
see here where suppliers can infect
在这里查看供应商可以感染的地方
reserve some slots to deliver pigs to a
预留一些插槽将猪运送到
food supply company and this idea of the
食品供应公司和这个想法
reservation is very particular because
预订很特别，因为
it starts every day at 10 o'clock at 10
它每天从10点的10点开始
o'clock people log into the system and
凌晨有人登录系统，
are able to start reserving slots for
能够开始为
the day after meaning that's at that
在那之后的第二天
time we get a rush because people want
我们因为人们想要而匆忙
to get the best slots best slots meaning
获得最佳插槽最佳插槽的含义
in their business is apparently in as
在他们的业务中显然是
soon as possible during the day and so
白天尽快等等
you see immediately when the application
您会立即看到该应用程序
starts
开始
at 10:00 the first loads get reserved
在10:00保留第一批货物
immediately and the other ones might get
立即，其他人可能会得到
a little bit less interesting of course
当然没那么有趣了
if you don't have a choice anymore then
如果您别无选择，那么
you have to take it but that's the ID
你必须要拿，但这就是ID
and then afterwards it's like maybe 10
然后大概是10
minutes of reservations and then
分钟的预订，然后
afterwards the application is more or
之后，应用程序更多或
less not used to rest of the day and so
少了一天不习惯
this is in fact a very interesting use
这实际上是一个非常有趣的用途
case where otherwise with a typical
在其他情况下通常
application the application would always
应用程序将始终
be up and running with this time we can
这段时间可以启动并运行
just when the application is not used
只是在不使用应用程序时
anymore we can just down scale we can
再也可以缩小规模
just say maybe just down scale all these
只是说可能只是缩小规模
serverless functions that we have and
我们拥有的无服务器功能
just don't pay for it at that time
只是当时不付款
because it's most of the time not
因为大多数时候不是
necessarily anymore there might be just
一定有可能只是
one or more individuals who still visit
一个或多个仍在访问的人
it but that's it so that's the ID and we
它，就是这样，这就是ID，我们
thought about well that's probably a
考虑好了可能是
good use case to get started with now if
如果现在就开始使用的好用例
you look at the architecture for this
你看一下这个架构
this is a kind of typical architecture
这是一种典型的架构
which you might find in a lot of
您可能会在很多地方找到
applications these days and so we have a
这些天的应用程序，所以我们有一个
server which runs an application which
运行应用程序的服务器
is typically layered and we have Valene
通常是分层的，我们有Valene
on the front end we have some service
在前端，我们有一些服务
layer so repositories and so on all the
这样的存储库等等
data is stored in an sequel database as
数据存储在后续数据库中
well and so that's the application that
好，那就是那个应用
we have here now the first thing that we
现在我们在这里有了第一件事
started with is that we wanted to move
首先是我们想搬家
out the application all the front end of
淘汰应用程序的所有前端
the application so what we did was move
该应用程序，所以我们所做的就是移动
out from Vardhan to an front end thick
从Vardhan到前端厚
clients technology with angular which we
客户技术与我们
started hosting on AWS s3 to be able to
开始托管在AWS s3上，以便能够
separate implementation a little bit
单独实施一点
back-end and front-end we also use JSON
后端和前端我们也使用JSON
server on the front end so that we can
前端的服务器，以便我们可以
mock out the back-end server and so that
模拟出后端服务器，以便
way we could start developing the front
我们可以开始发展前沿的方式
end independent of the back-end service
端独立于后端服务
now of course if it starts doing service
现在当然可以开始服务了
architecture we don't think about the
我们不考虑的架构
server anymore but instead we have to
服务器了，但是我们不得不
worry about how are we going to work out
担心我们要如何解决
this these layers that we had so we had
我们拥有的这些层
a service and a repository layer
服务和存储库层
including many classes there
那里有很多班
and we have to think about what is the
我们必须考虑什么是
the smallest amount of code that we want
我们想要的最少的代码
to put into a function we're going to go
放入一个功能，我们要去
into a little bit more detail later on
稍后再详细一点
but it's an interesting idea because the
但这是一个有趣的想法，因为
servlets architecture already makes you
servlets体系结构已经使您
think about small individual parts that
考虑一下小的单个零件
can communicate with each other using an
可以使用
account of an event-driven architecture
事件驱动架构的说明
and this kind of patterns we all know
我们都知道这种模式
that they can help us create reusable
他们可以帮助我们创造可重复使用的
components which are in turn very good
反过来又很好的组件
of course if you want to have loose
当然如果你想放松
coupling and high cohesion so that that
耦合和高内聚性
was an interesting thing but of course
是一件有趣的事情，但当然
these functions might have to operate
这些功能可能必须运行
with each other some functions might
彼此之间有些功能可能
call other functions and so we used AWS
调用其他函数，因此我们使用了AWS
step functions to combine them and we'll
步骤功能来组合它们，我们将
come back on it later as well underneath
稍后再回到下方
you can see there that we use terraform
您可以看到那里我们使用了Terraform
as an infrastructure s-code we also
作为基础架构S代码，我们还
talked a little bit later more on
稍后再谈
details for that part but it was very
这部分的细节，但它非常
easy to get started that way I will also
那样容易上手，我也会
see that that operation part is really
看到那个操作部分是真的
crucial if you want to develop these
如果您要开发这些至关重要
kind of applications and then of course
类型的应用程序，然后当然
there was this back-end as a service so
有这个后端即服务
we also integrated a lot of other
我们还整合了许多其他
services from AWS in this case to do all
在这种情况下，由AWS提供的服务
kinds of stuff like security like
诸如安全之类的东西
database access WebSockets and so on now
数据库访问WebSockets等等
again if we take a look at our example
再看一下我们的例子
before the migration we had a facade
在迁移之前，我们有一个门面
which in turn would call one or more
依次调用一个或多个
service methods and these might then
服务方法，然后可能
call multiple repositories so this is of
调用多个存储库，所以这是
course the facade is like the the
当然，立面就像
orchestrator you could say now if we
编曲家，如果我们现在可以说
translate that of it we thought about
翻译我们想到的
how we translate this to AWS to a
我们如何将其转换为AWS
service architecture and the first thing
服务架构和第一件事
that we thought about was of course we
我们想到的当然是我们
have this interface so we are going to
有这个界面，所以我们要
use an API gateway for that so in fact
为此使用API​​网关
the interface itself translates
接口本身翻译
one-on-one so it's so to say to the API
一对一，所以对API这么说
gateway now the implementation of the
网关现在执行
facade methods itself that was in fact
立面方法本身实际上是
the orchestration and
编排和
we used AWS step functions for that so
我们为此使用了AWS step函数
this is going to manage all these steps
这将管理所有这些步骤
that we have in this kind of methods and
我们在这种方法中拥有的
make sure that everything is provided
确保提供了一切
from one service to another in both in
从一项服务到另一项服务
our case from one function to another so
我们的案例从一个功能转移到另一个功能
that's what we see here and then of
那就是我们在这里看到的
course we have our data layer and the
当然我们有我们的数据层和
data layer is well you have multiple
数据层很好，你有多个
options there you could say we going
选项，你可以说我们要去
we're going to use also lambdas for that
我们将为此使用lambda
but we decided in fact to package the
但是我们实际上决定打包
data layer in one and multiple jars
一个和多个jar中的数据层
one for each repository that we had and
每个我们拥有的存储库一个
make that available as a library towards
将其作为图书馆提供给
our step function well towards our
我们的脚步朝我们的方向发展
functions using AWS layer functionality
使用AWS层功能的功能
so that way we can have a central
这样我们就可以拥有一个中央
location where we can share common
我们可以共享共同之处的位置
libraries with our alumnus now then we
现在与我们的校友一起图书馆
have to think about the programming
必须考虑编程
language and well the application itself
语言以及应用程序本身
was written in Java with spring
是用Spring用J​​ava编写的
technology so our initial idea was also
技术，所以我们最初的想法也是
let's not try to complicate things any
我们不要试图使事情复杂化
further and so let's also you start
更进一步，让我们也开始
using Java that way we can also reuse
使用Java这样我们也可以重用
some of the code very easily and of
一些代码非常容易
course also because of course we wanted
当然也因为我们想要
to use spring technology and spring
使用Spring 技术和Spring
cloud functions in particular for this
云功能为此特别
one we did switch a little bit towards
我们确实做了一点切换
the supportive services because those
支持服务，因为那些
functions we have written in no GS and
我们没有GS编写的功能，
that's of course one of the powers that
那当然是
you have with these functions you can
你有这些功能，你可以
just very easily choose the kind of
只是非常容易地选择
language that matches your needs
符合您需求的语言
depending what kind of functionality
取决于哪种功能
kind of knowledge that you have inside
你内在的知识
your company and so on so that's the
您的公司等等，这就是
approach that we chose here also one of
我们在这里选择的方法也是
the things is typically when you talk
事情通常是当你说话时
about Java and serverless or function as
关于Java和无服务器或功能
a service then well the cold start is
服务，然后冷启动是
often a problem because it takes a lot
通常是一个问题，因为这需要很多时间
of time to start it up but once it start
有时间启动它，但是一旦启动
up it's it's in fact faster when you
起来实际上是更快的速度
have a warm start so that's why we chose
有一个良好的开始，这就是为什么我们选择
for this and also we can just very
为此，我们也可以
easily for application preload functions
轻松实现应用程序预加载功能
at 10 o'clock in
在10点
morning make sure that they are hot
早上确保他们很热
started and that people can start using
开始，人们可以开始使用
an effect and afterwards if it takes a
效果，然后如果需要
little bit longer for this one or two
这个或两个更长一点
use cases what you have well was not
用例您所擅长的不是
such a big issue at a time and then just
一次这么大的问题，然后
very briefly we also chose for the AWS
简而言之，我们还选择了AWS
platform as you can see there are a lot
可以看到平台很多
of other possibilities
其他可能性
a lot of the on-premise possibilities
许多内部部署的可能性
they focus on kubernetes and Kay native
他们专注于kubernetes和Kay native
technologies but we chose for a public
技术，但我们选择了公众
cloud in this case AWS right so to move
云在这种情况下AWS正确，因此可以移动
on to our actual implementation so I'm
继续我们的实际实施，所以我
generally speaking there's three main
一般来说，主要有三个
parts or boss back-end as a service but
零件或老板后端作为服务，但
fast function as a service and finally
快速的服务功能，最后
operations so in this case I will start
操作，在这种情况下，我将开始
with fast because that is the main part
快速，因为那是主要部分
of the application and of course the
的应用程序，当然
main place where all the code is
所有代码所在的主要位置
happening so the basic definition of a
发生，所以一个的基本定义
llama so we start with llama which are
骆驼，所以我们从骆马开始
the functions on AWS so a llama is
AWS上的功能，因此
essentially a piece of code that will
本质上是一段代码，
run based on an input of jason and which
根据杰森的输入运行
in turn again returns an output of jason
依次再次返回jason的输出
and none was actually a correct to
而且实际上没有一个是正确的
events sources which can be a whole yeah
事件来源可能是一个整体
a whole bunch of other triggers and so
一大堆其他触发器等等
yeah you've got dynamic database
是的，你有动态数据库
triggers you've got Astri api gateway of
触发您具有的Astri api网关
course generally speaking llama is
当然，一般来说美洲驼是
always just jason in json out and yeah
始终只是jason in json out，是的
alumni will actually consist of a piece
校友实际上是由一块
of code that will then define its
的代码，然后将其定义
handler by a simple yeah yes string so
通过一个简单的处理程序是字符串
in this case function not reservation
在这种情况下功能不保留
not get handler is basically just a
没有获取处理程序基本上只是一个
simple yeah
很简单
class definition
类定义
so for to implement our lambdas at least
因此至少要实施我们的lambda
of Java ones we used sprinkler function
我们使用的洒水功能
so spring card function and it was
所以Spring 卡功能，它是
chosen because it offers us to basically
选择它是因为它为我们提供了基本
decouple from any specific bathroom so
与任何特定的浴室分离，因此
where is a double yes or a sure or open
双重肯定或肯定或开放在哪里
whisk is also supported we could
扫也受支持，我们可以
basically write our code independent of
基本上独立于
any platform on the other hand it and
另一方面，任何平台
also offers a very very uniform
还提供了非常非常统一的
programming model and of course it also
编程模型，当然还有
offers us to run standalone so we could
提供我们独立运行的功能，因此我们可以
eat in a sense just run our functions as
从某种意义上讲，就可以按照我们的职能运行
a simple spring boot app and use that to
一个简单的spring boot应用程序，并使用它来
yeah and test them locally that way and
是的，以这种方式在本地对其进行测试，
of course other spring boot features
当然还有其他 spring boot 功能
would also then be enabled because of
也将由于以下原因而被启用
course we're using spring so just to go
当然，我们正在使用Spring ，所以只是去
over this again so we've got our basic
再来一次，所以我们有了基本的
function definition which may be a bean
函数定义，可能是一个bean
and then we've got several cases here so
然后我们这里有几个案例
we've got an adapter which is an extra
我们有一个适配器，这是一个额外的
dependency you include to support a
您包括以支持
specific platform or we've got a basic
特定的平台，或者我们有一个基本的
spring setup which will either become a
Spring 的设置将成为
spring boot app with with rest support
带有启动支持的Spring Boot应用
or tasks or streams or whatsoever so a
或任务或流或其他任何东西
spoke of our dependencies already and
谈到我们的依赖
these are the ones you would need so
这些是您需要的，所以
you've got the basic spring flight
你有基本的 Spring 飞行
function context which is the core of
函数上下文是
spring cloud function and will basically
Spring Cloud 功能，将基本上
enable you to run a function while then
使您可以同时运行一个功能
spring class function adapter in this
Spring 类功能适配器
case a DES adapter will then start to
情况下，DES适配器将开始
cater towards a specific platform so
迎合特定平台，因此
there will be a small well there's
会有一口小井
always a small implantation cost but
总是很小的植入成本，但是
usually simply implementing an interface
通常只是简单地实现一个接口
without much work now when we talk about
现在当我们谈论很多工作时
implementation of course building is
课程建设的实施是
also one of the bigger issues so in this
这也是更大的问题之一
case we have two options so first one
情况我们有两个选择，所以第一个
would be the basic Wellspring option and
将是基本的Wellspring选项，并且
using maven to build a jar so to do this
使用Maven构建一个罐子，这样做
well we would build a jar preferably
好吧，我们最好建一个罐子
using the spring boot
使用 spring boot
like it may even begin which would allow
甚至可能开始
us to well create a jar that is
我们来创造一个罐子是
instantly runnable as with Java
与Java一样可立即运行
something that AWS actually also needs
AWS实际上还需要的东西
is however shading because well to
但是阴影是因为
improve startup times in general it is
通常可以缩短启动时间
best you actually shade all of our
最好你实际上遮蔽了我们所有的人
dependencies and place them directly in
依赖项并将它们直接放在
the class path so this is just an extra
类路径，所以这只是一个额外的
step that helps with that specifically
专门针对此步骤的步骤
for Atos again other option for building
再次为Atos构建
is actually Sam and this is actually
实际上是山姆，这实际上是
what we chose for in the end but which
我们最终选择了什么，但是
will be expanded upon with operations
将随着业务扩展
and so Sam is actually was actually used
所以山姆实际上被实际使用了
to package our functions as zips so Sam
将我们的功能打包为zip，所以Sam
also works slightly differently from the
也与
actually spring compiling of maven
实际上是Maven的 Spring 编译
compiling process as it doesn't actually
编译过程，因为它实际上并没有
allow us to run zip as a file it's very
允许我们将zip作为文件运行，这非常
so that Adel yes will interpret that zip
这样Adel yes就会解释该邮编
file and take care take note of the
存档并注意
handler which we defined earlier for the
我们之前为
lambda as a well as its entry point for
lambda以及它的入口
the function so again to make it
功能再次使它
actually work with spring we also need
实际使用 Spring ，我们还需要
an extra variable variable of main class
主类的额外变量
just to define where spring context
只是定义 Spring 的背景
exists so again this image so now
再次存在，因此此图像现在
actually to move on one layer up so we
实际上是向上移动一层，所以我们
went from alumnus and now we're actually
从校友那里走了，现在我们实际上
going up to step functions which are D
上一步是D
well the orchestrating of our llamas
以及我们的美洲驼的编排
into one process so here you actually
进入一个过程，所以实际上
have our example so sub functions are
有我们的例子，所以子功能是
defined as a simple definition so it
定义为一个简单的定义，所以它
basically is basically referring to
基本上是指
operating a flow a state machine of
操作流程的状态机
different lambdas and processes which
不同的lambda和过程
you will execute in order or even
您将按顺序执行，甚至
parallel there's a lot of options here
平行的，这里有很多选择
so yeah and there is multiple patterns
是的，有多种模式
that are allowed here such as to control
在这里允许诸如控制
the logic where you have choices and
您可以选择的逻辑和
service so in our example here you
服务，因此在我们的示例中，您
actually see the pre process box which
实际看到预处理框
will just perform a small change a
只会做一个小的改变
transformation on our input data
输入数据的转换
than the prevail edition which will
比盛行版
reduce some data which we need to
减少一些我们需要的数据
validate with the effective validation
通过有效验证进行验证
than a choice state evaluates validation
而不是选择状态评估验证
which will then choose well I go to
那我会选择的很好
invalid or I go to create an a creation
无效，或者我去创建作品
which would create our effective
这将创造我们有效的
reservation or soft reservation in our
我们的预订或软预订
system and then you've got notify which
系统，然后您会通知
will then notify connected clients of
然后将通知连接的客户端
the change that happened and here you
发生的变化，在这里你
see one of our valid flows so moving
看到我们有效的流量之一，如此动人
straight through to notify but only
直接通知但仅
following one path and finally testing
遵循一条道路，最后进行测试
testing is also of course important um
测试当然也很重要
everyone knows about well basic testing
大家都知道很好的基础测试
of micro services so use in general Java
微服务，因此可在一般Java中使用
code so you use unit test service tests
代码，以便您使用单元测试服务测试
and hopefully UI tests and yeah so in
并希望进行UI测试，是的，
general you have you'll have a unit test
一般而言，您将进行单元测试
for every class but this testing
除了这个测试，每个课
actually becomes even slightly more
实际上变得更多
skewed so the pyramid we have here
偏斜，所以我们在这里有金字塔
becomes a router skewed as you see right
成为您所看到的歪斜的路由器
here so because we're we're thinking in
在这里，因为我们正在思考
serverless
无服务器
functions and especially functions that
功能，尤其是那些
have to run on a platform it actually
必须在实际运行的平台上运行
happens more often that we will use a
发生的频率更高，我们将使用
function and especially test functions
功能，尤其是测试功能
and our systems on a more higher level
以及我们的系统处于更高的水平
so where we have actually already
所以我们实际上已经在哪里
deployed them to the system and then
将它们部署到系统，然后
test the entire flow in its well in this
在此测试其井中的整个流程
entirely entirety this actually helps
完全完整，这实际上有帮助
well because generally speaking there
好吧，因为一般来说
are a lot more concerns here about
这里还有更多的问题
actual hosting or rather not so much the
实际托管，或者不是那么多
hosting which is actually taking care
托管实际上正在照顾
for us but the actual working together
对我们来说，但是实际的合作
of the systems so those are extra steps
这些系统是额外的步骤
that need to be subtle
需要微妙的
so effectively there's a paradigm shift
如此有效地发生了范式转变
here where we will code locally and we
在这里，我们将本地编码，我们
can testing remotely and as you even
可以进行远程测试，甚至
said testing on production so now for a
说生产测试，所以现在
short demo so we're just going to go
简短的演示，所以我们就去
through some of the code of our
通过我们的一些代码
functions so I've got the basic get
功能，所以我有基本的
reservations function so of course our
预订功能，所以我们当然
app will need to well retrieve
应用程序需要很好地检索
reservations and this is what will do it
保留，这将是做什么
so
所以
we've got yeah one second I'm gonna zoom
是的，我要一秒钟
that so all you can see better right
这样你就可以看到更好的权利
does it work
它有效吗
all right I see thumbs up behind so
好吧，我在后面看到竖起大拇指
right so um initially well we've got a
对，所以最初我们很好
basic spring class no this looks very
基本的 Spring 班，不，这看起来非常
basic but there's actually two options
基本的，但实际上有两个选择
here again we could run this as a bit as
再一次，我们可以像这样运行
a spring boot application now you see
一个Spring Boot应用程序，现在您看到
here if configuration which means it
在这里，如果配置意味着它
wouldn't actually be able to run as a
实际上将无法以
spring application right right of this
Spring 申请权
moment right so we've got a basic start
正确的时刻，所以我们有了一个基本的起点
now this is also something different
现在这也有所不同
usually you see your spring application
通常你会看到你的 Spring 申请
now this isn't just a spring application
现在这不仅仅是一个 Spring 应用
it's a functional spring application
这是功能性的Spring应用程序
which means it is tailored towards being
这意味着它是专门为
a function and nothing else what it
一个功能，别无所求
means is well among others that we're
在我们当中，这意味着很好
actually gonna define our context
实际上会定义我们的上下文
ourselves because it is this small it's
我们自己，因为它很小
actually well it's more efficient for
实际上很好，对于
boot for startup that we don't actually
启动我们实际上并不启动的启动
rely on component scanning and
依靠组件扫描和
whatsoever to initialize our context
任何初始化我们上下文的东西
after all is just one function as we
毕竟，这只是我们的一项功能
find here so yeah this is some of
在这里找到，是的，这是一些
technical mojo but yes so basically just
技术魔力，但是的，所以基本上
reducing one being a function
减少一个功能
registration which will then be passed
注册，然后将通过
our actual function which an intern is
我们实习生的实际职能是
faster with reservation repository
保留库更快
defining input and output types as well
定义输入和输出类型
then we have our function itself so
那么我们有自己的功能
it'll just perform a call to our
只会打电话给我们
reservation repository get reservations
预订库获取预订
based on input from yet so the in which
根据尚未输入的信息
was a reservation query and then finally
是预订查询，然后终于
yeah just definition of our reservation
是的，只是我们的预订的定义
query itself now this is actually not
现在查询本身实际上不是
enough to just run this on say llama or
足以在说骆驼上运行
any other platform so we need to
任何其他平台，所以我们需要
implement our adapter which is what
实现我们的适配器是什么
happens in an handler class now you see
现在在处理程序类中发生
this is zoom this is very small and it
这是变焦镜头，非常小，
doesn't actually need anything more than
实际上并不需要什么
this so we just implemented and
因此，我们刚刚实施了
providers interface or class from from
提供者接口或来自的类
spring so be spring boot request handler
Spring ，所以成为 Spring 引导请求处理程序
which in turn will then implement the
然后依次实施
interface for needed for the lambda
Lambda所需的接口
Edelen slumber system then yeah just to
Edelen睡眠系统然后是的
go over it so what we saw here again was
走过去，所以我们再次在这里看到的是
a call to a repository now we perform
现在调用存储库
the well.you we use a library paradigm
好吧。您使用图书馆范式
where every repository was becoming a
每个存储库都变成一个
separate library and then we imported
单独的库，然后我们导入
that library so what we have here is
该图书馆，所以我们在这里是
actually just basic spring gdb see again
实际上只是基本的Spring gdb再次看到
we use gdb see templates here for me
我们使用gdb在这里查看模板
merely for a dependency reduction
仅用于减少依赖
because after all having a function run
因为毕竟有一个功能运行
and have to load in a lot of libraries
并且必须加载很多库
again is a cost for startup so yeah we
再次是启动的成本，所以我们
have some basic yeah so create
有一些基本的知识，所以创建
reservation and get reservation method
预订并获取预订方法
here with implementation nothing special
这里的实现没有什么特别的
there and then yeah a basic definition
然后是一个基本定义
of the actual reservation class so far
到目前为止的实际预订舱位
for code demo and then we're gonna move
进行代码演示，然后我们将继续
on to the backend as a service which I'm
到后端作为我的服务
gonna leave to you okay so we have seen
会留给你好吧，所以我们已经看到
how we can create our functions now of
我们现在如何创建功能
course as I said before we have this
正如我之前所说的，当然
integration with a lot of services
与很多服务集成
probably as well and the first thing of
大概也是，第一件事
course that we had to do was take a look
我们要做的当然是看看
at the database we stayed at an sequel
在数据库中，我们待续
database we started using Postgres which
我们开始使用Postgres的数据库
was managed in the cloud itself using
在云端本身使用
Amazon RDS so that was the first move we
Amazon RDS，这是我们的第一步
did of course the migration itself from
当然做了迁移本身
the data itself went very smoothly
数据本身非常顺利
and the other thing was of course we
当然，另一件事是我们
have to connect with that database so we
必须连接到该数据库，所以我们
have to make sure that we get the
必须确保我们得到了
credentials also for that we had to use
我们也必须使用的凭据
or we could use it over secrets manager
或者我们可以通过秘密管理器使用它
or we have of course some things like
或者我们当然有一些事情
vault and stuff like that so you can of
像这样的 Vault 和东西
course choose whatever you like but
当然选择任何你喜欢的但是
again not to be stuck with managing it
再次不要被管理
ourselves we started using a managed
我们自己开始使用托管
service here as well and then to connect
也在这里服务，然后连接
everything together the requests coming
所有的一切都来了
into the lambda functions and step
进入lambda函数和步骤
functions we are we chose to use API
我们选择使用API​​的函数
gateway for that and for security
安全网关
reasons of course we also made use of
当然，我们也利用了
Amazon Cognito which is in fact also
Amazon Cognito实际上也是
making sure that our WebSockets secure
确保我们的WebSockets安全
is securely
安全地
and as you can see the client itself is
如您所见，客户端本身就是
going to request a token from its
要从其请求令牌
service and then of course with every
服务，然后当然
requests we provide this token which is
要求我们提供此令牌，该令牌为
then going to be checked against the
然后要对照
service itself for validity now the only
唯一有效的服务本身
thing that we had left to do was keep
我们剩下要做的是保持
some more states as we said before the
正如我们在之前所说的那样
serverless application itself can be
无服务器应用程序本身可以是
started very easily and very quickly but
非常容易，非常迅速地开始，但是
can also be shut down so we can't really
也可以关闭，所以我们不能真正
cool store anything in them and so of
酷存储任何东西在他们等等
course for being able to store all the
能够存储所有
clients that were connected towards our
与我们联系的客户
application so we could send updates
应用程序，以便我们可以发送更新
wait to store them externally from the
等待从外部存储它们
functions and we chose Amazon DynamoDB
功能，我们选择了Amazon DynamoDB
for that and together with the laminas
为此，并与薄板一起
itself in node GS so every time we get a
本身在节点GS中，所以每次我们得到一个
reservation it's going to check the
预订它将要检查
animal to be for all the connected
动物是所有连接的
clients and it's going to contact the
客户，它将与
API gateway to send out a WebSockets and
API网关发送WebSockets和
message towards those clients now
现在向这些客户发送消息
everything about operations maybe before
有关操作的一切，也许之前
we continue because you might think that
我们继续，因为您可能会认为
service now means we don't have any
现在的服务意味着我们没有任何服务
operations at all but that's of course
完全没有操作，但这当然是
not true in fact sometimes it can make
事实并非如此，有时它可以使
it a little bit harder
有点难
of course you don't really have to care
当然，您不必在乎
about the management of a service
关于服务的管理
anymore but a distributed application
不再是分布式应用程序
comes with a lot of extra things that
附带了很多额外的东西
you have to take care of so you have to
你必须照顾好所以
make sure that you have distributed
确保您已分发
monitoring for example so that if
监视例如
something goes wrong you can very easily
出问题了，您可以很容易地
figure out where it's where the fault is
找出故障所在
happening of course all the things like
当然发生了所有类似的事情
security you have a lot of things going
安全，您有很多事情要做
on regarding logging and so on so there
关于日志记录等等，等等
are a lot of things that you have to
有很多事情要做
take care of which are still your
照顾那些仍然是你的
responsibility and you can of course use
责任，您当然可以使用
some tools for that but that's of course
一些工具，但是那当然
it's not going away now for the
现在并没有消失
operations in the sense of
某种意义上的操作
infrastructure s codes we started with
我们开始的基础设施代码
terraform and this is in fact helping us
地形，这实际上在帮助我们
to set up our infrastructure our
建立我们的基础设施
resources that we need for this
为此我们需要的资源
environment and it's a multi-platform
环境，这是一个多平台
infrastructure as code meaning that you
基础架构作为代码意味着您
can have one templates that contains
可以有一个包含以下内容的模板
resources for different platform
不同平台的资源
and also is going to store the states
并且还将存储状态
independently of the platform meaning of
独立于平台的含义
course that is going to check out what
当然要检查什么的课程
kind of resources are already deployed
已经部署了一种资源
at that time so that it doesn't well
在那个时候，所以不好
that he can be very smart in only doing
他只会做的很聪明
the updates and not having to redeploy
更新，而不必重新部署
everything all the time now one problem
现在所有的一切都一个问题
that we encountered here was that at a
我们在这里遇到的是
certain moment we started to implement
某一刻我们开始实施
the WebSocket support and so we had to
WebSocket支持，所以我们不得不
use the API gateway for that and that
为此使用API​​网关
was in fact not yet support it in
实际上还不支持
terraform at the time and that's of
当时的地形
course because there are firm needs to
当然是因为有坚定的需要
keep up to speed with all the platforms
与所有平台保持同步
and the new functionalities that come
以及随之而来的新功能
out there and they can run behind a
在那里，他们可以在后面跑
little bit so that's one of the problems
一点点，这就是问题之一
that we discovered with terraform and
我们用terraform发现的
later on effects
稍后的效果
well we one solution could be of course
好吧，我们一个解决方案当然是
that we have one terraform file for most
大多数情况下只有一个terraform文件
of the things and then just want cloud
的东西，然后只想要云
formation for example for that but
例如形成，但
that's of course doesn't really feel
那当然不是真的
right and so later on we in fact
对，所以后来我们实际上
switched towards cloud formation
转向云形成
entirely to do our infrastructure s code
完全是为了做我们基础架构的代码
also some as I said before is going to
我之前说过的一些
help us with a building so it's doing
帮助我们建造一座建筑物
the built automation but it's doing lots
内置的自动化系统，但它做的很多
more than that it can also help us to do
不仅如此，它还可以帮助我们做
local testing local testing with some
本地测试与一些本地测试
mocking not that much but you can mock
嘲笑不多，但你可以嘲笑
the API gateway for example and you can
例如API网关，您可以
also have a local DynamoDB instance if
也有一个本地DynamoDB实例，如果
you want to in the end we didn't really
你想最终我们不是真的
use this a lot because of the fact that
由于这个事实，经常使用
it's Owen
是欧文
only going to work if your API gateway
仅在您的API网关有效时
is rather simple but in our case we have
很简单，但就我们而言
to define our own API gateway setup
定义我们自己的API网关设置
because we had this WebSocket support
因为我们有了WebSocket支持
and so on that is needed so and as also
等等都需要
some built-in best practices for example
一些内置的最佳做法，例如
you can do gradual deployments or you
您可以进行逐步部署，也可以
say I'm going to direct the 10% of the
说我要指挥10％的
traffic towards a new version of my
流量向我的新版本
function and if everything goes right
功能，如果一切正常
then we can do more but if maybe some
那么我们可以做更多，但如果有的话
alerts pops up then automatically we can
警报弹出然后我们可以
roll back to the previous version so
回滚到以前的版本
that we can find out what's going on
我们可以找出正在发生的事情
so in fact some uses its own templating
所以实际上有些使用了自己的模板
ID above CloudFormation meaning that is
CloudFormation上方的ID表示
going to
即将
translate his same template into a cloud
将他的相同模板转换成云
formation one on the left side you can
可以在左侧编队一
distinguish the same template because
区分相同的模板，因为
there is a transform element in there
那里有一个变换元素
meaning that AWS is going to have to do
意味着AWS必须要做
a translation step towards cloud
迈向云的一步
formation and then you can have your
阵型，然后你就可以拥有你的
resources as you can see here we define
如您所见，我们在此处定义了资源
a function for getting the reservations
获取预订的功能
it's based on a runtime Java 8 and it
它基于运行时Java 8，
has a link towards the API gateway with
有一个指向API网关的链接
a path slash reservation and HTTP method
路径斜线保留和HTTP方法
gets so that way we define all our
这样我们就定义了所有
resources and we can start deploying
资源，我们可以开始部署
this into our environments now in fact
实际上，这已经进入我们的环境
for our rather simple example here you
对于我们这里的简单示例
can see that there is already a lot of
可以看到已经有很多
things going on here and the main thing
这里发生的事情和主要的事情
I want you to notice here is that of
我要你注意的是
course you don't really want to set this
当然你真的不想设置这个
up yourself through the console and this
通过控制台设置自己
needs to be automated as much as
需要尽可能地自动化
possible this is a small application but
可能这是一个小应用程序，但
if you start using this for larger
如果您开始使用这个更大的
applications then this is really
应用程序，那么这真的
mandatory to have it automated as much
强制使其尽可能自动化
as possible you can see some numbers up
尽可能看到一些数字
there regarding our stuff and then of
关于我们的东西，然后
course one template that rules or
当然，一个规则或
manages them all another couple of
管理他们另外两个
things which we're not going to go into
我们不会去做的事情
much detail here but of course you also
这里有很多细节，但是当然你也
need to take care of CI CD we are
需要照顾CI CD
looking at this moment at AWS also for
此刻还在AWS上寻找
some support in that one because it has
在那方面有些支持，因为它有
nice integrations with SEM and also
与SEM的良好集成
monitoring of course we have default
监控当然我们有默认值
monitoring with cloud watch but you are
使用Cloud Watch进行监视，但是您
also looking into more detailed logging
也正在研究更详细的日志记录
towards AWS x-ray which is going to help
对AWS X射线有帮助
us with that as well and I think that's
我们也一样，我认为那是
bringing us to a final demo right so for
将我们带到最终演示版，以便
the final demo I'm actually gonna take
我实际上要拿的最后一个演示
you all through the console and show
大家通过控制台显示
some of the well essentially resources
一些本质上很好的资源
that we've now deployed using our Sam
现在我们已经使用Sam进行了部署
tablet yeah so let's just start off at
平板电脑是的，所以让我们从
the bottom so we've got a function
底部，所以我们有一个功能
essentially here so this is the alumni
本质上是这里，所以这是校友
console we've got several functions here
控制台，我们在这里有几个功能
most of these are actually node yes as
其中大多数实际上是节点yes
you can see but we've
你可以看到，但我们已经
a couple in numbers and I'm just gonna
几个数字，我只是
grab one so you get reservation function
抢一把，你就可以预约
between show earlier
之间显示较早
um and this is actually all that it is
嗯，这实际上就是全部
so right here you've actually got plenty
所以在这里你实际上有很多
of options so you can perform tests at
选项，以便您可以在以下位置执行测试
this point we can also just run if you
此时，如果您也可以运行
change some parameters on this but this
改变一些参数，但这
is all managed for us so right now we've
都是为我们管理的，所以现在我们已经
actually just taking this put is all of
实际上只是把这个看跌期权
all of this in our template or Sam
所有这些都在我们的模板或Sam中
template and as such it just appears
模板，就这样出现
here for us this is of course useful if
在这里对我们来说这当然是有用的
you have to debug or there's a and any
你必须调试或有一个和任何
errors or whatsoever that happened of
错误或发生的任何事情
course this is the place to go and
当然，这是去的地方
actually find what's happening you
真正找到正在发生的事情
notice some specific things so first of
注意一些具体的事情，所以首先
all as I said earlier there's some
就像我之前说的，有一些
specific needs we need because we're
我们需要的特定需求，因为我们
building a spring app with Sam one of
与Sam一起构建spring应用程序之一
the those would be email us so one of
这些将通过电子邮件发送给我们，因此其中之一
those would be the main class which now
这些将是现在的主要阶层
Devon defines which class actually
德文郡实际上定义了哪个类
contains our spring context and another
包含我们的 Spring 背景和另一个
would be function name which is actually
将实际上是函数名称
required to define the bean that spring
需要定义那个 Spring 的bean
is gonna Oh assumed as a function to be
被认为是一个函数
run for the summer so it would
跑夏天，所以它会
essentially be possible to for example
本质上是可能的，例如
combine multiple functions in one jar
在一个罐子里结合多种功能
and then deploy them all together and
然后将它们全部部署在一起
define which one should run with this
定义哪个应该与此一起运行
parameter also some other stuff so
参数还一些其他的东西，所以
secret names which is for the sequence
序列的秘密名称
manager which was mentioned and then
被提到的经理，然后
yeah just a Dec URL for database moving
是的，只是一个用于移动数据库的Dec URL
on to step functions so here you
继续执行功能，所以在这里您
actually see in small our entire process
实际上只看到了我们的整个过程
it's this so this is the definition over
就是这个，这就是
state machine so you see a whole bunch
状态机，所以你看到一大堆
of states define now again this might
州现在再次定义这可能
differ for platform so well step
平台的差异很大
functions uses this but again google cut
功能使用此，但再次谷歌切
functions or as you may have their own
功能或您可能有的功能
implementations for this and yeah so
的实现，是的，所以
this is a hold flow that is defined
这是定义的保留流程
which effectively evaluates to
有效地评估为
this this graph so um yeah so we got
这个图，所以嗯，所以我们得到了
again I went over this
我又去了
so pre-processing which we for eval date
所以我们要进行评估
validate etc and I'm actually gonna
验证等等，我实际上会
perform a quick run do also show
执行快速运行也显示
something else so let's see if we go
还有其他事情，让我们看看是否
here look at our execution so you see
这里看看我们的执行情况
we've got a bunch of them I'm gonna copy
我们有一堆我要复制
this one change one parameter because
这一改变一个参数，因为
things need to be different for
事情需要有所不同
validation to work and we're just gonna
验证工作，我们将
start this and we're actually gonna see
开始这个，我们实际上会看到
live how this is now running so yeah
直播现在如何运行，是的
this is effectively live now so we've
现在有效了，所以我们已经
got a function running our several
有一个功能运行我们的几个
functions and you can actually see the
功能，您实际上可以看到
process of start up here so there's
在这里启动的过程，所以有
actually two states for Alana to being
实际上阿拉纳有两个州
is either hot or cold okay not the Katy
是热还是冷都可以，不是凯蒂
Perry song but yeah so and so how good
佩里的歌，可是，某某有多好
mean Alana is actually already active
意味着Alana实际上已经活跃
and running in an existing machine while
并在现有机器上运行
Colton would mean it is currently
Colton表示目前
inactive and needs to start up first
无效，需要先启动
Jessica so a so-called cold start and
杰西卡所谓的冷启动和
which as you see is occurring now so
如您所见，现在正在发生
this lambda took awhile I mean it is it
这个lambda花了一段时间我的意思是
which written in Java which means cold
用Java编写的意思是冷
starts will take longer than for example
开始将花费比例如更长的时间
an interpreted language lambda written
写成的解释语言lambda
in node or Python or whatsoever but then
在节点或Python或任何东西，但然后
again we've got the advantage of because
再次，我们有优势，因为
it's actually compiled language it will
它实际上是编译语言
run faster once it started so yeah we'll
一旦开始运行就更快，是的，我们会
see this flow going through now so yeah
看到现在流过，所以是的
we're true validate and now create which
我们是真正的验证者，现在创建
again is starting up and this is
再次启动，这是
actually also very useful UI because we
实际上也非常有用的UI，因为我们
can actually click on every each of the
实际上可以点击每个
states and look what was inputted and
状态，看看输入了什么，
working out right here so create has
在这里工作，所以创建有
finished and now notifies running and
完成，现在通知运行和
notifies dawn and her flow has completed
通知黎明，她的流程已经完成
and then now I'm actually gonna just run
然后我实际上要跑了
the same code so this should now fail
相同的代码，所以现在应该失败
and show our failure failure flow as
并显示我们的失败失败流程为
such and you'll see it was actually
这样，你会看到它实际上是
already finished because each and every
已经完成了，因为每个
one of those llamas was now actually
这些美洲驼之一实际上是
already active and as such could just be
已经活跃，因此可能只是
accessed immediately
立即访问
and finally we've got our API gateway so
最后我们有了我们的API网关
the API gateway which perhaps wasn't
API网关，也许不是
explained very well but is essentially
解释得很好，但本质上是
our port to the Internet so if some of
我们的互联网端口，如果
our front-end application wants to
我们的前端应用程序想要
access and this one it will actually
访问，这实际上
yeah arrive here and then from here on
是的，到达这里然后从这里开始
out we can send our send messages H bars
出来我们可以发送我们的发送消息H条
HTTP requests and send them to the
HTTP请求并将其发送到
appropriate function or step function
适当的功能或步进功能
that they have to go through so yeah and
他们必须经历这样，是的，
then finally and I've actually forgot to
然后最后，我实际上忘记了
open this so you're gonna see some more
打开这个，你会看到更多
internals here we have our actual
内部在这里，我们有我们的实际
front-end application which is hosted in
托管在其中的前端应用程序
a simple bucket on a stream two
流两个简单的桶
properties here and here and then
此处和此处的属性
reserved and then we actually have our
保留，然后我们实际上有
ready-made application right here and if
现成的应用程序就在这里，如果
we say like well right actually do use
我们说很好就可以使用
the buttons validation all right and
按钮验证没事，
reserve and then should return receive a
保留，然后应该返回接收
message here hopefully I assume demo is
消息在这里我希望演示是
a never go right again yeah so
一个永远不会再正确了，所以
apparently this one doesn't want to work
显然，这个人不想工作
right now but well I guess something has
现在，但是我想有些事情
to go wrong
出问题了
so anyways um that would be then the end
所以无论如何，那将是结束
of the demo I hope you all enjoyed and
我希望大家都喜欢这个演示
let's go on to your conclusion
让我们继续您的结论
[Music]
[音乐]
all right so we still have a conclusion
好的，所以我们仍然有一个结论
but you can see they have already
但是你可以看到他们已经
clipped so you can just leave after the
剪裁，所以您可以在
conclusion no problem so just to
结论没问题，只是为了
summarize some things up here this was
在这里总结一些事情是
not really a walk in the park as maybe
也许不是在公园里散步
we would have expected it to be there is
我们本来希望它在那里
a lot of things going on here and this
这里和这发生了很多事情
is a distributed application we know
是我们知道的分布式应用程序
that from micro services of course and
当然来自微服务
there there's a lot of things going on
发生了很多事情
there of course when you make it more
当然，当您使它更多时
granular and put it on the function
细化并放在函数上
level then of course that complexity can
然后当然可以使复杂度
only increase because you now have more
只会增加，因为您现在有更多
things to manage and in fact the
要管理的事情，实际上是
management is still one of the things
管理仍然是事情之一
that are for this kind of application
用于这种应用
quite simple but again if you have large
很简单，但是如果您有很多
applications figuring out what is the
应用程序弄清楚什么是
capabilities that you have in your
您拥有的功能
application it's kind of like a real
应用程序有点像真实的
thing that you have to care about so
你必须关心的事情
that especially if you have a large
特别是如果你有一个大
development team that everyone knows
每个人都知道的开发团队
what kind of functions you have
你有什么样的功能
available what kind of capabilities are
可用的功能是什么
in there how can we retrieve them how
在那边我们怎么找他们
can we find them and so on also we
我们可以找到他们吗，等等
experience that there is well there is
有好的经验
some documentation available of course
当然有一些文档
but there is not that much guidance in
但是其中没有太多指导
best practices and how to handle things
最佳做法以及处理方式
there are of course some frameworks that
当然有一些框架，
already have some kind of idea about
已经有一些想法
this well we didn't actually look at the
这个嘛，我们实际上并没有看
serverless framework but it is one of
无服务器框架，但它是其中之一
the things that we want to look at and
我们想要看的东西
of course we just looked at sem which is
当然，我们只是看了sem
already giving us some direction but
已经给了我们一些指导，但是
still there is a lot of work going on
仍然有很多工作要做
there and a lot of things that can
那里有很多东西可以
improve in my opinion also the
我认为也有所改善
operations especially for deploying with
操作，尤其是用于部署
multiple versions and stuff like that
多个版本之类的东西
that is something that SEM can handle
这是SEM可以处理的
but still to to propagate changes
但仍在传播变化
towards different environments and stuff
针对不同的环境和事物
like that you most of the time have to
就像你大多数时候
do a lot of manual setup still now the
现在仍然进行很多手动设置
idea of this architecture is kind of
这种架构的想法是
nice as we said before it forces you to
正如我们之前所说的那样，它迫使您
think about these small units that's
考虑一下这些小单位
communicate with each other but it also
互相交流，但同时
have some yeah you have some
有一些，你有一些
responsibilities there as well to make
还有责任
sure of course that the things that are
当然可以肯定的是
valid for a distributed application that
对符合以下条件的分布式应用程序有效
you also apply them here things like
您也可以在这里应用它们，例如
idempotent stateless strands
幂等无状态链
stuff like that we also have to think
这样的东西，我们也必须思考
about this because it's not very easy if
关于这一点，因为这不是很容易
you if you just neglect these kind of
你，如果你只是忽略这些
things but then again you can make use
事情，但话又说回来，你可以利用
of reusability because now you have
可重用性，因为现在您有了
these different functions that you can
您可以使用这些不同的功能
just start using in different step
只是开始在不同的步骤中使用
functions for example using these state
功能，例如使用这些状态
machines our ID if you want to go and
机加工我们的身份证，如果你想去
look into this try to focus on one
看这个尝试专注于一个
platform to start with because it's easy
平台开始，因为它很容易
to get lost we as well in preparation
迷路了，我们也在准备中
for this talk started to look in all
这个谈话开始在所有
kinds of stuff and we really wanted to
各种各样的东西，我们真的很想
make this about the entire architecture
涉及整个架构
well is your gonna get lost anyway at
好吧，你无论如何都会迷路
that time so start small start with one
那个时候从一个开始
platform use one tool to build your
平台使用一种工具来构建您的
stuff and then go from there that's a
的东西，然后从那里去
very good idea too to start with I think
我想也是一个很好的主意
and as I said before you still have to
就像我之前说过的
think about operations if you're not
如果不是，请考虑一下操作
doing operations right now or you're not
现在就做手术，否则就不做
really into the DevOps part you really
真的融入了DevOps部分
are going to be forced to do it you if
将被迫这样做，如果你
you don't have to or if you don't handle
您不必或如果您不处理
your micro service at this time in a
您此时的微服务
proper way with all the operations that
所有操作的正确方式
come along with it you're not going to
伴随它，你不会
do it good in a function as a service
发挥服务的作用
platform because it's going to get even
平台，因为它会变得平整
worse there so start looking into those
更糟糕的是，所以开始调查那些
things and then a gov of course for the
事情，然后当然是政府
code itself well the language is really
语言本身就是很好的代码
up to you of course depending on what
当然取决于您
you are used to maybe but again you have
你习惯了，但又有一次
this very flexible way of defining
这种非常灵活的定义方式
multiple languages and you can combine
多种语言，您可以结合
them just the way you like it so start
他们就是您喜欢的方式，所以开始
make use of that as well so mix if you
也要利用它，如果您混合使用
need to but of course as we are really
当然需要
focus on the Java language it is a nice
专注于Java语言，这是一个不错的选择
language but keep in mind of course this
语言，但请记住这一点
idea of the cold starts which might be
冷启动的想法可能是
an issue for some applications so I
一些应用程序的问题，所以我
think that concludes our talk so are
认为这结束了我们的谈话
there any questions at this moment yes
此刻有任何问题是
so can you repeat again can you check
所以你可以再重复一次吗
x-ray to know what happened to the
X射线了解发生了什么
application give us but we actually
应用程序给我们，但我们实际上
haven't got x-ray configured right now
现在还没有配置X射线
but I could check glide one card watch
但我可以检查滑行一卡手表
to see what's going on there
看看那里发生了什么
oh if you absolutely want it come on so
哦，如果您绝对希望这样的话
that's one of the things that we're
这是我们要做的事情之一
still looking into more details so at
仍在寻找更多细节，因此
this moment we're using mainly cloud
此刻，我们主要使用云
much to monitoring everything well the
很好地监控一切
basics over our Landis but the x-ray is
Landis的基础知识，但X射线是
allowing us to go even further so we
让我们走得更远，所以我们
briefly looked into it but we have not
简要调查了一下，但我们没有
really rolled it out for this
为此真的推出了
application at the moment question here
现在的应用程序问题在这里
why w AWS was it a technical decision or
为什么AWS是技术决定或
was it given well it was more or less
如果给予得当，或多或少
like a decision of multiple things first
像是先决定多件事
of all we had some experience already in
我们已经有了一些经验
the platform because last year we also
该平台，因为去年我们还
did an application there using apps
使用应用程序在那里做了一个应用程序
engaging effect and abstraction on top
引人入胜的效果和抽象
of service and otherwise as well because
服务以及其他原因
there is good community out there and
那里有一个好的社区，
most of the time good documentation
大多数时候，好的文档
involved
涉及
well it's sometimes you run into some
好吧，有时候你碰到一些
troubles but I think the other platforms
麻烦，但我认为其他平台
might even have it more difficult there
那里甚至可能更困难
so that's that were the main two reasons
这就是两个主要原因
that we that we looked into AWS at this
我们在此调查了AWS
time but when using now the abstraction
时间，但是现在使用抽象
that we have in spring we should be able
在 Spring 我们应该能够
to transfer the functions very easily
轻松转移功能
infect so if one time we find out that
传染，所以如果有一次我们发现
another platform might be better at the
另一个平台可能会更好
time you can just very easily swap that
时间，您可以非常轻松地交换
out of course the services might be a
当然，服务可能是
bigger problem because of course they
更大的问题，因为他们当然
will have to be
将必须是
figure it and see what we have there
弄清楚它，看看我们在那里
right so to answer the previous question
对，以便回答上一个问题
I do my it works now yeah we have we
我现在就开始运作，是的，我们有
have notices earlier that when cold
早些时候有通知
sores happen sometimes well the actual
有时会发生疮，实际
response in the front end doesn't work
前端的响应不起作用
that well so and it isn't handled as
这样很好，它不被处理为
such but yeah generally speaking our
这样的，但是总体来说我们
function does work fairly well but the
功能确实运作良好，但
functions work but the front end may
功能正常工作，但前端可能
need some improvements again that wasn't
再次需要一些没有的改进
the focus I have another question why
焦点我还有一个问题，为什么
are we forced to test a lambda function
我们是否被迫测试Lambda函数
directly in a base if we are using a
如果我们使用的是直接在基地
spring framework we can create a kind of
Spring 的框架，我们可以创建一种
integration or a unique test I guess it
集成或独特的测试，我猜是
is possible to perform certain mocking
可以执行某些嘲笑
and such to actually integrate and test
并进行实际整合和测试
in in yeah just just locally that's true
是的，只是在本地，这是真的
but in the end it's mostly because the
但最后主要是因为
actual environment we're running on
我们正在运行的实际环境
might change something so for us it
可能会对我们有所改变
would actually be that we actually had
实际上是我们实际上拥有的
to well perform trial and error to
很好地进行反复试验
actually get a Sam built spring function
实际上得到了山姆内置的Spring 功能
actually working on there so certain
确实在那里工作
things that might not be thought about
可能没有想到的事情
such as the main class environment
如上课环境
variable we're needed to get it to work
变量，我们需要它才能正常工作
and we're actually well we didn't find
我们实际上很好，我们没有找到
it documented anywhere so that was one
它记录在任何地方，所以那是一个
of those things and it might just be
这些东西，可能只是
something that happens and if you don't
发生的事情，如果你不这样做
test it on the platform then yeah you
在平台上测试它然后是的
might come across the surprises so also
可能会遇到惊喜，所以
there you have to pay attention but I
那里你要注意，但我
think it's a good practice of course if
认为这当然是一个好习惯
you can do try to do as much integration
你可以尝试做尽可能多的整合
test locally because they are rather
在本地测试，因为它们相当
cheap to do of course but again you will
便宜当然可以，但是你会再次
have to in our pin you have to deploy it
必须使用我们的销钉，您必须部署它
once to that form to then of course make
一次到那个形式然后当然
sure that everything runs there um so
确保一切都在那里运行，所以
what are these
这些是什么
what are these change some things that's
这些改变什么是
a little vague
有点模糊
like what's actually going to have what
像什么会真正拥有什么
what things could a WS actually change
WS实际可以改变什么
for your functions well it's not so much
对于您的功能来说不是很多
that AWS changes the function it's more
AWS改变了功能
so how it runs it so I'm where well
所以它如何运行，所以我在哪里
spring generate well or may even which
Spring 会产生好，甚至可能
generates a jar which would get then run
生成一个罐子，然后将其运行
on a platform
在平台上
it could even run on a double yes it's
它甚至可以双倍运行，是的
more so that well how Sam builds so 81
这样山姆如何建造好81
Sam builds our function is in the form
山姆建立我们的职能是形式
of a zip and it actually just well drops
拉链，实际上滴得很好
our classes in well a fairly simple
我们的课程相当简单
format into the zip as well as all
格式化成zip以及所有格式
dependencies needed the way it works is
需要依赖的方式是
that set well in that form
以这种形式设置的很好
AWS will actually look for our handler
AWS实际上会寻找我们的处理程序
which we defined for the function in in
我们在中为功能定义的
there and then the handler will be
在那里，然后处理程序将
initialized booted up and will then
初始化启动，然后
start looking for a spring context now
现在开始寻找 Spring 背景
that's where it would actually go wrong
那才是真正出问题的地方
because they couldn't find one since it
因为从那以后他们找不到一个
wasn't booted up as a normal Java spring
没有作为正常的JavaSpring 启动
app so that's where that went wrong for
应用程序，所以这是错误的地方
us so yeah that was the main problem
我们，是的，这是主要问题
discards at this moment I think the rest
此时此刻我会丢弃
of the things looks really good to test
看起来真的很好测试
it locally first essentially the codes
首先是本地代码
is still the same it's more so how it is
还是一样，更是如此
run and what what the entry point to the
运行以及什么是入口
code is so yeah and how it started up in
代码是如此，它是如何启动的
that sense okay so yeah maybe just one
这种感觉还可以，所以也许只有一个
more question and yes please
更多问题，是的，请
yeah so we do use a single repository um
是的，所以我们只使用一个存储库
well for mainly ease of wealth purses of
主要是为了缓解
meze of we have versioning and
我们有版本控制和
whatsoever although we do have right so
尽管我们确实有权利
continue yeah so yeah so as I was saying
继续，是的，所以是的，正如我所说的那样
we do have everything in the same
我们确实拥有一切
repository but we do use sub modules in
仓库，但我们确实在
this case and while a maven parent-child
这种情况下，而一个maven的亲子
structure to actually organize our
实际组织我们的结构
functions okay so we're out of time I
功能还可以，所以我们没时间了
see so thank you very much
看到所以非常感谢你
if you have more questions please come
如果您还有其他问题，请来
and talk afterwards
然后说
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]